largearticle.com 2017-12-20

# Large Article » Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which large article collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the http://largearticle.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Large article.

Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

Web browser cookies

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

How we use collected information

Largearticle may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:  
– To improve our Site  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.  
– To send periodic emails  
We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.  
How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

Google Adsense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Changes to this privacy policy

Large article has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Content Publishing and Copyright Information**

By creating an account on [www.largearticle.com](http://largearticle.com/), you or the user acknowledge to accept all the terms and conditions of www.largearticle.com. We keeps on updating Terms and Conditions from time to time, to keep them updated all time which suits best of interest for all concerned and related parties. You or the user will be notified via registered email address, whenever there is an update.

www.largearticle.com does not publish any content or any media on its own and it is only a medium to present the content posted by its various registered users. Although we try our best to keep only authorized and legitimate content to be posted on our website. Having an account with us or by registering an account with us, user fully acknowledges to have the proper authorization or have the copyrights for the content or any media that is posted on www.largearticle.com.

As we just said www.largearticle.com. Is just a medium for its users and we try our best to keep only the authorized or the legitimate content on our website. www.largearticle.com or any of its subsidiaries or its owners or employees held no responsibility for any content/article/media that is published on www.largearticle.com and www.largearticle.com reserves full rights to disable/ delete/ hide or take down any content that is posted on www.largearticle.com.

Which types of work are subject to copyright?

# Written works, such as lectures, articles, books, and musical compositions

# Visual works, such as paintings, posters, and advertisements

#  Audiovisual works, such as TV shows, movies, and online videos

# Sound recordings and musical compositions

#  Video games and computer software

#  Dramatic works, such as plays and musicals

A user may post his Ideas, facts, and processes on www.largearticle.com. As a reader i.e. who is reading the content on www.largearticle.com, you are sincerely advised to check the correctness, authenticity and genuineness of the content. Neither www.largearticle.com nor any of associates takes responsibility or any loss or damage that can be or is caused by the content.

We hope you will enjoy association with us and will have a fruitful relationship with us.

Further or any further concerns or clarification, you can contact us a

Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:
